你的体重是...113.9磅
you weight is,hm... 1-1-3.9 pounds.
不要逼我伤害你
Are you gonna make me hurt you?
我可不想
I didn't think so.
你还好吗?
Are you all right?
我伤着你了吗?
Did I hurt you?
Bob!
Bob,出什么事了?
Bob,what's wrong?
怎么了? 跟我说话啊
What happened?,Talk to me.
哦, 天哪, 亲爱的,坚持住, 坚持住
Oh,my god. Okay,honey,,hang on,hang on.
这里是911,您的紧急事件是?
911.What is your emergency?
是的, 我们需要一辆救护车,Xavier路10600号4b单元
Yes,we need an ambulance,at 10600 xavier,unit 4b!
我丈夫喘不动气了
My husband can't breathe.
哦, 天啊!
Oh,my god!
他的脸开始发青,你必须马上过来!拜托了, 快点!
He's turning blue.You have to send someone now!Please,hurry!
你在吹头发?
You blow dry your hair?
哦, 不好意思, 我吵醒你了吗?
Oh,sorry,did I wake you up?
你在吹头发?
You blow dry your hair?
请原谅我真的在乎我的外表
Excuse me for actually caring,what I look like.
我觉得你应该用的词是“痴迷”
I think the word,you're looking for is obsessing.
你用了快一个小时了
Been at it for almost an hour.
如果你也想用, 只要说就是了
If you wanted in,,all you had to do is say so.
我不想, 我想睡觉
I don't want in.I want sleep.
不管怎么说也到了起床时间了
It's about time you got up anyway.
将近九点了
It's almost 9:00.
这可不行
This isn't gonna work.
- 什么?,- 你, 住在这儿
- What?,- You. Staying here.
你要把我赶出去?
You're kicking me out?
就住了一晚?
After one night?
怎么了, 你觉得我们,应该先去试试心理咨询?
What,you think,we should try counseling first?
你到底为什么想睡在沙发上呢?,你有钱
Why do you want to,sleep on a couch anyway? You got money.
至少在离婚完成之前
At least until the divorce is finalized.
明天我就不会再烦你了
I'll be out of your hair tomorrow.
就剩今天一天了
What's left of it.
那是三天前
It was three days ago.
我的喉咙变得很干
My throat got really dry
然后我的舌头就像气球一样肿起来了
and then my tongue felt like,it was blowing up like a balloon.
我猜已经查过食物过敏了吧?
I assume somebody,checked for food allergies?
嗯, 前两个医生, 他们都查了
Well,the first two doctors,both did.
第三个说是恐慌症
Next one said it was a panic attack.
下一个想要摘除他的扁桃体
The one after that,wanted to take his tonsils out.
最后一个不知道,只是告诉我们找House医生
The last one had no idea.Just referred us to dr. House.
病历上说发作之前,你在进行某种激烈的体力活动
It says the attack was preceded by,some sort of strenuous physical activity.
呃... 是的
Um... yeah.
你当时在干什么?
What were you doing?
太棒了, 舌头肿大的性爱狂
Awesome.A sex being with a swollen tongue.
想想所有我可以让Forman去搜的地方
Just think of all the places,I can make foreman search.
他不是性爱狂
He's not a sex being.
他是个幸福的已婚男人
He's a happily married man.
没这种人
No such thing.
你在干什么?
What're you doing?
测验新的咖啡因传输系统
Testing a new caffeine delivery system.
他没能睡成他的美觉
He didn't get his beauty sleep.
Wilson搬进去了而且很明显,他有异乎寻常吵人的习惯
Wilson's moved in and,apparently has unusually loud toenails.
如果他们喜欢强奸幻想的话,菜单上也会有S&M
If they're into rape fantasies,,s&m is on the menu as well.
颈部外伤会导致声带痉挛,又会导致哽噎
Neck trauma could cause vocal,chords paroxysms,which could cause choking.
我没看见有外伤的迹象,而且声带明显的是张开的
I didn't see any sign of trauma,,and they were remarkably open.
我问了性传播疾病,他们..
I asked about stds,and they...
承认几个月之前参加了一次“三人行”
admitted participating,in a threesome a few months ago.
一百元赌他们的生活跟下一对一样惨
Hundred bucks says they're,as miserable as the next couple.
- 另外一个, 男的还是女的?,- 女的, 他老婆的大学室友
- Another guy or girl?,- Girl. His wife's college roommate.
如果他的婚姻不幸福的话,我想不出谁是了
If he's not happily married,,I don't know who could be.
他们在找寻什么
They're looking for something.
如果你很幸福的话,你就不用再寻找什么了
If you're happy,,you got nothing to look for.
他老婆把安排这个当作周年庆礼物
His wife arranged it,for an anniversary present.
要是你问我, 如果两个人真信任彼此
And if you ask me,,if two people really trust each other,
每七年左右玩一次“三人行”,真的能对婚姻有所帮助
a threesome once every seven years,might actually help a marriage.
好了, 我说我们停止鉴别诊断,开始讨论我们的意见吧
Okay,I say we stop the ddx,and discuss that comment.
我赌
I'll take the bet.
可能第一个医生是对的
maybe the first doctor was right.
食物过敏解释了所有的过敏性反应
a food allergy explains the anaphylaxis.
可能是神经上的问题
Could be neurological.
进行性延髓麻痹能解释这些症状
Progressive bulbar paralysis,would explain the symptoms.
不可能  肌萎缩性脊髓侧索硬化症在,影响他的咽喉之前会先影响面部肌肉
No. Als would affect,his facial muscles before his throat.
如果毛病不是出在他的咽喉呢?
What if the problem's not in his throat?
考虑到所有的症状都出在那儿,这么想真是有点奇怪
That'd be a little odd considering,that's where all his symptoms are.
- 指谁?,- 病人
- Says who?,- The patient.
既然大部分病人连尺骨和肛门都分不清
Since most patients,can't tell their ulna from their anus,
我猜这家伙也不知道
I'm guessing this guy,also doesn't know the difference
噎住与窒息之间的不同
between choking and suffocating.
他的咽喉可能没事,而他的肺可能会一团糟
His throat might be fine.His lungs might be messed up.
再抽点血,做个胸部CT,还有全身的体积扫描图
Get more blood,a chest ct,,and a body plethysmograph.
当然了, 除非你认为我们应该先问问,病人他的肛门在哪里
Unless of course,you think we should be,asking the patient where his anus is first.
感觉, 呃, 感觉我非得上厕所,然后当我试着去小便的时候...
It,uh,feels like I have to urinate,,and then when I try to go...
穿上你的裤子
pull up your pants.
- 是前列腺的问题, 是吗?,- 不  不是前列腺
- It's prostate,isn't it?,- Nope. Not your prostate.
- 是疱疹,- 疱疹?
- Herpes.- Herpes?
疱疹
Herpes.
该你了
Your turn.
如果这能让你觉得好受点
If it makes you feel any better,
到这儿来的病人,一半都有点这种真菌感染
half the patients who come into this place,have some sort of crotch rot.
呃, 不, 不是那样的
Uh,no,it doesn't.
听着, 这不可能,我结婚都二十年了
Look,this is impossible.I've being married for 20 years.
二十年来你做过爱吗?
You had any sex for 20 years?
是啊, 当然--
yes,of course-
那这就是你怎么得的
then that's how you got it.
我只和我妻子做爱
The only person,I've had sex with is my wife.
真失败
Bummer.
每天服用一次
Take this once a day.
告诉你老婆也这么做
Tell your wife to do the same.
这药不能治愈它,但能减少发作的频率
It's not gonna cure it,,but it'll less the frequencbreaks.
但肯定有些误解
But there must be some mistake.
- 你有孩子吗?,- 有啊
- You got any kids?,- Yeah.
他们有人上吉他课吗?
Any of them take guitar lessons?
- 没有,- 网球,艺术, 表演?
- No.- Tennis,art,acting?
我女儿学空手道,为什么这么问?
My daughter does karate.Why?
把这个给她师父吧
Give this to her sen**
哦, 等一下
oh,wait.
- 你老婆打网球吗?,- 不打
- Does your wife play tennis?,- No.
我也这么想
That's what I figured.
再证实一下没什么错
It never hurts to make sure.
给那个教练吧
For miyagi.
我现在要开始拍片子了,我要你大口喘气  就像狗那样
I'm gonna close the shutter now.I need you to pant. Kind of like a dog.
很好 继续
That's good. Keep going.
我能问你一个私人问题吗?
Can I ask you a personal question?
呃, 我猜行吧
Uh,I guess.
那个, 呃, 三人行
The,um... the threesome.
还有...角色扮演
And... the role playing.
是因为生活开始变无聊了吗?
Is that because things get boring?
不是
No.
我们只是在...享受我们的幻想
We just... enjoy our fantasies.
- 你结婚了吗?,- 没
- You married?,- No.
你可以重新开始做深呼吸了
You can go back to,taking the deep breaths now.
婚姻失败并不是因为夫妇俩觉得厌烦了
Marriages don't fail,because couples get bored.
它们失败是因为...
They fail because...
在人们约会的时候, 会伪装成他们认为
while they're dating,,people pretend to be the person
伴侣想要的那种人而且...
they think their partner wants and then...
嗯, 你只能保持那么长时间
well,there's only so long,you can keep that up.
也许约会的阶段他们就是那样的人,但他们会改变
Maybe they are that person,while they're dating,but then they change.
人们觉得他们的伴侣会变?
People thinking their partner will change?
这是婚姻之所以失败的另一个理由
That's another reason marriages fail.
人们不会变的
People don't change.
至少不会是实质性的改变
At least not in any way,that really matters.
我觉得你喝的咖啡因够用了
I think you've had enough caffeine.
你是对的, 不是他的咽喉 是他的肺
You were right. It's not his throat.It's his lungs.
体积扫描图显示肺容量下降
Plethysmograph revealed,decreased lung capacity.
CT显示肺上有斑痕
and the ct showed lung scarring.
绝对是间质性肺纤维化
It's definitely,interstitial pulmonary fibrosis.
不确定的是病因
What's not definite is the cause.
没有关节炎, 没有结节病
There's no arthritis, no sarcoidosis.
呃, 他不服用任何处方药
Uh,he's not on any prescription ms.
而且他是个婚礼摄影师
And he's a wedding photographer
所以我不认为工作的时候他会暴露在,煤尘或是石棉环境中
so I doubt he got exposed,to coal dust or asbestos at work.
- 病因可能是先天的,- 不可能是先天的
- Cause could be idiopathic.- Can't be idiopathic.
- 先天的是指没有已知病因的,- 我指的是--
- Idiopathic means without a known cause.- What I meant was that-
你指的是你不知道病因是什么
what you meant was,you don't know what the cause is.
说出来,  我们就可以避免这次谈话了
Just say that,,and we can avoid this conversation.
没有掌声?
No applause?
- 他现在情况怎么样了?,- 很稳定
- What's his current condition?,- Stable.
- 那我们可以等等,- 等什么?
- Then we can wait.- Wait for what?
等那个你找不出来的东西,来引起其他症状
For whatever you can't,figure out to cause something else.
你知道那会的
You know it's going to.
间质性肺纤维化有可能会继续--
It's possible the ipf,could just continue to-
他的皮肤有点不正常
There's something wrong with his skin.
- 好了, 不要抓了 我得看看,- 我做不到! 这要把我逼疯了
- Okay,stop scratching. I gotta look at it.- I can't!This is driving me crazy.
- 别抓了我才能--,- 让它停下来!
- Stop scratching so-,- make it stop!
好的
Okay-
让它停下来 让它停下来
make it stop!,Make it stop.
现在我们有可讨论的了
Now we got something to discuss.
什么既能导致肺部斑痕也能造成,发痒的红色小水疱
What causes both lung scarring,and the itchy splotchy red blotchies?
明显不是对药物的反应
It's obviously not a reaction to medication.
我们还没给他药呢
We haven't given him any yet.
但是除去明显不是的原因
But what besides,what it's obviously not
还有什么能引起肺部斑痕和,发痒的红色小水疱
can cause both lung scarring,and the splotchies?
你要去哪儿?
Where are you going?
完成咖啡因传输系统的第二部分
To complete the second half of,the caffeine delivery system.
大点声说话, 要不然就进来
Either talk louder or get in here!
进去出来都是同一个颜色
Same color coming out as going in.
你觉得这是个营销问题吗?
You think that's a marketing thing?
狼疮能引起肺部斑点和皮疹
Lupus could cause lung scarring and a rash.
或者可能还是食物过敏
Or it could still be a food allergy.
- 我们已经排除了过敏症了,- 是吗?
- We've already ruled out allergies.- Did we?
Cameron呢?
Where's cameron?
我们在男洗手间
We're in the men's room.
我们这儿需要位过敏症专家!
We need an allergy expert in here!
这可以稍等两分钟
This can wait two minutes.
你怎么知道
You don't know that.
Chase认为食物过敏依旧有可能
Chase thinks that food allergies,should still be on the table.
不, 那解释不通肺部斑痕
No,it wouldn't,explain the lung scarring.
某些顺势疗法的研究发现了
Some homeopathic studies,have found a connection
食物过敏和自身免疫反应之间的关系
between food allergies,and autoimmune reactions
那可能会引发肺炎
which could cause,lung inflammation.
是啊  还有一些顺势疗法的研究发现
Yeah. And some homeopathic studies,have also found
磨碎了的蜘蛛能治癌症
that ground-up spiders can cure cancer.
- 我可以走了吗?,- 不行
- Can I go now?,- No.
肺, 皮肤 皮肤, 肺
Lungs,skin. Skin,lungs.
皮肺?
Sklungs?
肺, 皮肤
Lungs,skin.
咽喉
Throat.
重金属的毒性
Heavy metal toxicity.
解释了肺的问题、瘙痒
It explains the lungs,the itching.
舌头和咽喉的肿大
The swelling in his tongue and throat.
我原以为你不觉得他的咽喉,有什么不正常的
I thought you didn't believe,there was anything wrong with this throat.
我从没说过我不那么觉得
I never said I didn't believe it.
我只是说我有很好的理由去怀疑它
I just said I had good reason to doubt it.
那么现在呢?
And now?
现在我有很好的理由去怀疑那些怀疑
Now I have good reason,to doubt those doubts.
去嚼墙上掉下来的漆,病人的年纪也太大了吧
Patient's a little old,to be chewing paint off the walls.
他也不喝井水也不每天都吃鱼
Nor does he drink well water,or eat fish every day or do anything else
或者干其他的能暴露在重金属下的事情
that could've exposed him to heavy metals.
他和他老婆策划了一个婚礼,上个月在Cabo San Lucas举行的
He and his wife worked a wedding,in cabo san lucas last month.
很多墨西哥陶器的颜料都含铅
A lot of pottery in mexico,is contaminated with lead-based paint.
现在你还不高兴你进来了吗?
Now aren't you glad you joined us?
去搜搜他们家,还有验血和头发查铅
Search their house,and screen his blood and hair for lead.
顺便查查汞和砷
And test for mercury,and arsenic while you're at it.
Chase.
Chase
搞清楚度假区的厨师用什么做饭
Find out what the resort cooks with,
如果最近他们有重新粉刷,或是更换了什么管道
and if they have repainted,recently d any plumbing repairs.
我不会说西班牙语
I don't speak spanish.
那就真有挑战性了
Then it'll be challenging.
上帝啊
Good lord.
这是什么气味?
What is that smell?
填充的青椒
Stuffed pepper.
填充的什么?
Stuffed with what?
呕吐物?
Vomit?
本以为你会去旅馆呢
Thought you were going to a hotel.
我找了间公寓
I found an apartment.
我可以在周一搬,对你来说够快了吗?
I can move in on monday.Is that fast enough for you?
今天星期几?
What's today?
- 你从哪儿弄的这些东西?,- 嗯, 不是从你的厨房
- Where'd you get all that stuff?,- Well,not from your kitchen.
除了灌装浓汤和花生酱你不吃别的吗?
Don't you ever eat anything,besides canned soup and peanut butter?
难道你只吃这些?
Don't you eat anything,that doesn't look like
就像是屎壳郎滚到你盘子里的东西?
it's been rolled onto,your plate by a dung beetle?
尝尝
Try it.
很好吃, 是吗?
It's good,isn't it?
不
No.
只是比看起来好吃而已
Just better than it looks.
你觉得得吃多少用含铅颜料,上色的陶瓷罐子里
How much beans and rice,do you think you'd have to eat
盛的豆类和稻米
from a ceramic pot painted,with lead-based paint
才会有足够多的铅进入你的体内,并且损害你的肺?
to get enough lead into,your system to damage your lungs?
- 我们实在说孩子还是成年人?,- 成年人
- Are we talking a child or an adult?,- Adult.
那我会说非常多
Then I'd say a lot.
你得每天都吃豆类, 吃上几个月
You'd have to beans,every day for months.
你为什么这么爱看新扬基作坊?,（木工类电视节目）
Now,why do you have a season,pass to the new yankee workshop?
一个十足的笨蛋拿着动力工具干活
It's a complete moron,working with power tools.
什么东西会比这个更富悬疑性?
How much more suspenseful can you get?
- 我在-我刚才在看节目,- 不...
- I'm-I was watching something.- No...
你刚准备看节目
you were about to watch something.
我现在在看
I'm watching something.
看见不同之处了?
See the difference?
如果水被污染了,我岂不是也应该病了?
If the water was contaminated,,wouldn't I be sick too?
人代谢毒素的速度是不一样的
People can metabolize toxins,at different rates.
当然我们也会化验的
We'll test it to be sure.
- 最近有什么新装修吗?,- 没有
- Have you done any recent renovations?,- No.
有虫子或老鼠的问题吗?
Have any problem with bugs or rodents?
只是偶然有些蚂蚁
Just the occasional ant.
- 用喷雾杀虫剂了吗?,- 没  我讨厌那个气味
- Use bug spray?,- No. I hate the smell.
幸好我们俩都比较注意保持整洁
Luckily both of us are pretty,anal about keeping things clean.
是啊, 看得出来
Yeah,I can tell.
你觉得是蚂蚁的问题?
You think ants are the problem?
你能不能停下一秒钟,别往你嘴里面塞薄饼了
Can you stop stuffing your mouth,with pancakes for one second?
这些不是薄饼
These aren't pancakes.
这是澳大利亚坚果仁薄饼,Wilson做的, 好吃极了
These are macadamia nut pancakes.Wilson made 'em and they're amazing.
他说她不用喷雾剂, 但--
She said she doesn't,use bug spray,but-
一美元的天堂切片
silver dollar slices of heaven.
有些蚂蚁是有毒的 也许--
Some ants are poisonous.Maybe-
我不想要72处女了
forget the 72 virgins.
如果我要在一家拥挤的餐馆里,实行自杀式袭击
I blow myself up,in a crowded restaurant,
我就先点一盘这个
I'm gonna be asking,for a plate of these babies.
蚂蚁是大而红的还是小而黑的?
Is the ant big and red,or small and black?
中等棕色的
Medium and brown.
哈莉·贝瑞的棕色,还是比昂斯的那种棕?
Halle berry brown or beyonc brown?
有区别吗?
Is there a difference?
军蚁在几个小时之内就能吞噬、分解,吃掉一头牛
Army ants could devour,dissolve,,eat a cow in a matter of hours.
澳大利亚大蚁却是恶心的小杂种
Australian bull ants on,the hand are nasty little bastards,
但比起威胁, 它们更多的是讨厌,一点都不令人惊讶
but they're more of a nuisance than,a threat. No surprise there.
比昂斯那种
Beyonc?
好, 那就不是了
Well,then that's not it.
在度假区他吃了多少粘土?
How much clay,did he eat at the resort?
那是个五星级, 四百块一夜的地方,他们不用陶瓷罐子烹饪
It's a five-star,400-a-night place.They don't cook with ceramic pots.
- 毒性报告?,- 没证据表明有铅、汞或是砷
- Tox screen?,- No evidence of lead, mercury,or arsenic.
再做一次 打电话给休假地,找些不满的员工再谈谈
Run them again. Call the resort.Find some disgruntled employee to talk to.
- 再回到他家里--,- 不是重金属
- Go back to the home-,- it's not heavy metals.
- 症状说是的,- 化验说不是的
- The symptoms say it is.- The tests say it's not.
那么, 你相信哪个?,症状还是化验结果?
Well,who you gonna believe?,The symptoms or the tests?
- 可能是次食物过敏,- Cameron说不是的
- Could also be a food allergy.- Cameron says it's not.
如果你的结果错了, 她的为什么就不能?
If your tests can be wrong,,why can't hers?
他的饮食自从是个孩子起就没变过,他最喜欢吃玉米薄片
His diet hasn't changed since he was a kid.His favorite food is corn flakes.
我想他就着牛奶一起吃,成人最普遍的食物中毒诱因之一
Which I assume he eats with milk,one of,the most common adult onset food allergies.
开始按铅中毒治疗。 这是最可能的重金属
Start treating him for lead poisoning.It's the most likely heavy metal.
还有, 嗯, 你可以去测他是否对,乳制品、小麦还有豆类过敏
And yeah,you can test him,for allergies for dairy,wheat,and legume.
我没跟我女儿的空手道导师有一腿
I am not having an affair,with my daughter's karate instructor,
也不是我传染给我丈夫疱疹的
and I did not give my husband herpes.
去找House
Found out where house is.
如果你确信是过敏症
If your convinced it's allergies,
为什么你给他治疗铅中毒的药?
why're you giving him drugs,to treat lead poisoning?
我们现在还不确定
We're not convinced of anything,yet.
我想要别的, 这种乳霜不管用
I think I need something else.This cream isn't working.
我们在尽一切努力
We're doing everything we can.
- 对不起,- 不不, 不是我的背, 是我的脚
- Sorry.- No,no,it's not my back. It's my feet.
我觉得进浴室的时候踩到什么东西了
I think I stepped in something,when I went to the bathroom.
呃, 在我的袜子上 好疼啊!
Uh,it's on my socks.It's burning!
我什么也没看见
I don't see anything.
- 请把我的袜子脱下来,- 等等, 等等,等等, 等等,
- Please take my socks off.- Wait,wait,wait,wait.
停! 停! 停!
Stop. Stop,stop!
你用什么去挠他了?
What did you just scratch him with?
如果是过敏反应, 应该会出现在背上,而不是脚上
if there was an allergic reaction,,it'd be on his back,not on his feet.
- 疼死了! 求求你, 让它停下来,- 需要加巴喷汀（治疗神经病理性疼痛）
- Oh,god,it's burning!Please make it stop.- Gonna need some gabapentin in here.
下肢出现剧烈疼痛
excruciating pain in the lower extremities.
不是食物过敏的症状
Not a sign of a food allergy.
意味着有神经问题
Means there's a neurological problem.
更显著的是
More significantly,
这是另外一个经典的重金属中毒的标志
it's yet another classic,sign of heavy metals.
我刚刚又作了一次发检和血检
And I just did yet another,hair and blood test for lead
来检查铅还有其他任何他可能,暴露在之下的物质
and everything else he,could possibly have been exposed to.
全都是阴性
They're all negative.
肯定是别的什么
It's gotta be something else.
- 狼疮可能导致,- 不是
- Lupus could cause-,- no.
狼疮恶化得更缓慢,还会有关节疼痛
Lupus progresses slower.There'd be joint pain.
所以这不是个典型的例子
So it's not a typical case.
- 我们应该做次抗核抗体检测,- 不是狼疮
- We should get an ana,- it's not lupus.
症状不相符
Symptoms don't match.
化验结果不符合重金属中毒
And the tests don't match heavy metals.
又来了 他没法呼吸了!
it's happening again.He's not breathing!
舌头肿大, 气管关闭
Tongue's swelling,airways closing.
他得不到氧气了
'S not getting any air.
- 他的肺没问题,- 我们必须要做气管插管
His lungs are clear.We're gonna have to intubate.
Bob, 放松, 这个会帮助你呼吸的
try to relax,bob,,this is gonna help you breathe.
哦, 天哪!
Oh,my god!
他会吸进去的。 吸出来!
He's gonna aspirate. Need suction!
- 怎么了?,- 吸出来!
- What's happening?,- Suction.
太多呕吐物了,我们不可能插管的
there's too much vomit.We're never going to be able to intubate.
- 我们要做人造气管术,- 他不呼吸了
- We need to trach him.- He's not breathing.
他尿里的蛋白质和红细胞含量升高了
his urine has elevated,proteins and red blood cells.
是狼疮引起的肾衰竭
It's lupus-induced kidney failure.
- 如果我们不开始治疗的话...- 重金属的毒性会引起呕吐
- If we don't start treatment..- heavy metal toxicity could cause vomiting.
狼疮肾炎也会, 而且还会导致组织肿大
And so would lupus nephritis,,and it also causes tissue swelling.
他被他的舌头噎住了, 不是他的脚
He's choking on his tongue,not his feet.
我们给他治疗炎症的类固醇,能引起面部肿大
the corticosteroids we gave him to control,the inflammation can cause facial swelling.
依旧不是他的咽喉, 但你们离得很近了
It's still not his throat,,but you're getting closer.
我要做抗核抗体检测和血清培养
I'm doing an ana and a serum compliment.
如果你那么确定,干吗浪费时间做这些实验?
If you'r so sure,,why we waste time with tests?
开始治疗就是了
Just start treatment.
哦,等等 我们不能那么做,因为我们已经那么做了而且不起作用
Oh,no,wait,we can't do that because,we already have and it's not working.
- 因此...- 类固醇不是治疗狼疮肾炎
- Ergo...- corticosteroids aren't the only treatment
的唯一方案
for lupus nephritis.
我们还可以试试环磷酰胺,或者免疫抑制剂
We could also try,cyclophosphamide or immunosuppressants.
但只有我们用抗核抗体检验, 血清培养
Only if we confirm the diagnosis,with an ana,serum compliment,
抗DNA抗体检验, 静脉肾盂造影,或肾活组织切片试验确定诊断结果才行
anti-dna,iv pyelogram,and kidney biopsy.
那现在突然间你又相信试验了
So now you suddenly believe in tests?
- 这些症状-,- 这些症状都指向重金属中毒
- The symptoms-,- the symptoms all point to heavy metal poisoning.
是啊, 我们都明白这个
Yeah,we all get it.
除非你有证据又能告诉我是哪种重金属
Unless you've got proof and can tell me,which heavy metal it is,
我就开始对狼疮的治疗方案了
I'm starting treatment for lupus.
全身红斑性狼疮导致免疫系统过度活跃
systemic lupus erythematosus causes,the immune system to become hyperactive.
会攻击正常的人体组织
Attack normal tissue.
这可能是肺部发炎和喉部肿胀的原因
It could be what caused the lung inflammation,as well as the swelling in his throat
并且开始破坏他的肾脏
and now what appears,to be damage to his kidneys.
通常用类固醇治疗
The treatment's usually steroids.
但他已经在用了呀
But he's already on steroids.
如果试验证明我们是对的
If the tests confirm,we're on the right track,
我们可以尝试其他的药物
there are other medications,we can try.
如果不起作用呢?
And if those don't work?
狼疮是慢性症状
Well,lupus is a chronic condition,
通常可以控制
but it's generally controllable.
什么叫通常?
What do you mean,generally?
罕见的情况是心肾衰竭
In rare cases,it can cause,cardiovascular or renal failure.
心以及...肾?
Cardiovascular,and... renal.
那是指心脏和肾脏对吧?
That's,uh,the heart,and the kidneys,right?
是的
Yeah.
不要着急
Don't worry.
会好起来的
It'll be all right.
喜欢么?
Enjoying the salad?
没放生菜
There's no lettuce.
我知道里面没有生菜
I'm aware that there's no lettuce!
想知道我是怎么知道的么?
Do you know,when I obtained this knowledge?
我正在享受...
- Actually,I'm in the middle of-,- when I made it.
在我拌沙拉的时候,为我自己做的
For myself.
我怎么会知道?
Well,how was I supposed to know?
本来我以为...
Well... I was hoping-
这个能提醒你,(纸条: "别碰我的午饭")
this might tip you off.
这很自私 你不觉得么?
That's kind of selfish.Don't you think?
我说了我帮你做一份,你说不要
I offered to make you some.You said no.
呵呵,那是在我尝过烙饼以前
Ah,that was before I tasted the pancakes.
我这是在称赞你,你应该感到高兴
It's a compliment,,you should be flattered.
给你
Here.
Lambert太太的疱疹测试结果
It's mrs. Lambert's herpes test results.
谁的太太?
Mrs. Who?
你告诉过很多病人,他太太和女儿的空手道老师上过床?
You've told more than one patient
想要煽风点火就要清扫战场
You wanna stir the pot,,you have to clean up the mess.
你如果得了疱疹会怎么做?
What would you do if you got herpes?
她五点准时过来,不要让我来催你
she's coming in at 5:00,,don't make me come looking for you.
我知道你会怎么做
actually,I know what you'd do.
-但是我觉得一个正常的男人...- 还有别打电话过来请病假
- But I mean a normal guy-,- and don't be calling in sick,
或者说你的团队需要你
or saying that your team needs you
去做什么紧急会诊
for some kind emergency consult.
如果他怀疑他的老婆有可能也有外遇
If he suspected that maybe his wife,had also been playing pickle games,
他不会说出来
he could just keep it on the down low.
直到她也被传染
At least wait till she got infected.
你把疱疹传染给妻子只为了转移视线?
You'd give your own wife herpes,just to shift the blame onto-
如果他得了疱疹,甚至会传染给亲生母亲
oh,he'd give his own mother herpes,if it got him out of clinic duty.
可能就是太太出轨了
Of course, maybe it was the wife.
也许她才是...
Maybe she was the one who-
Nympho太太在哪?
where's mrs. Nympho?
在外面,怎么了?
- She's waiting outside.- Why?
好好查一查她
Go search her.
查她的医疗记录么？
What,you mean her medical records?
不是这个意思,这可是个搜查她的好机会
If I meant that,,good chance i'd have said that.
你认为她在下毒?
You think she's poisoning him?
他应该已经开始好转
His symptoms should be,getting better the longer he's here.
但是却越来越糟
Instead they're getting worse.
要么她在下毒要么...
So either she's poisoning him or-
重金属不是病因.
it's not heavy metals.
我们已经排除了10种重金属了
We've done over ten,different heavy metal tox screens-
再试剩下的30种也没什么意义
because there's no reason,to test for the other 30.
毒素不通过空气和食物传播,除非有人放入你的体内
They don't get into the air or food.
要想知道她搞什么鬼就要搜查一下
And the only way,we're going to find out
我不想因为荒谬的理论指控谁谋杀亲夫
I am not going to accuse a woman,of trying to murder her own husband
已经排除了其他可能性
We've eliminated,every other possibility.
我们没有排除掉所有的可能性
We have not eliminated,every other possibility.
狼疮疗法有任何效果么?
Has he responded to,the latest lupus treatment?
只过了几个小时
He's only been on it,for a few hours.
他没有反应因为这不是狼疮
He hasn't responded,because it's not lupus.
这不是过敏,肌肉萎缩,,关节炎或是肉状瘤病
It's not allergies,als,,arthritis,or sarcoidosis.
她才是唯一的原因
She's all that's left.
去查
Do it!
我是House医生
I'm dr. House.
我能看一下你的包吗?
Mind if I take a look in your purse?
为什么?
Why?
因为我要搜一下
Because I'm going to,need to search it
还要搜你,看你怎么下的毒
and you for whatever,you're using to poison your husband.
为什么我要伤害我的丈夫?
Why would I want to hurt my husband?
那你不会介意我搜一下吧
Then you won't mind if I search your things.
搜吧
Go ahead.
满意了?
You satisfied?
当然不行了
Absolutely not.
她同意我搜查所有地方
She agreed to,let me search everywhere else,
除了那里,你不觉得可疑吗?
but this she says no to.Doesn't that tell you something?
这说明她不想让一个神经错乱,的医生拿着手电筒在她阴道里找东西
Yes,that she doesn't want some lunatic doctor,searching her vagina with a flashlight.
- Cameron可以啊,-我才不会...
- Oh,cameron could do that.- I'm not going to-
她进医院以来就没出去过
the woman hasn't left,the hospital since they arrived.
不管她用了什么,她肯定藏起来了
Whatever she's using,,she's obviously hiding somewhere.
她没有下毒
She's not poisoning him.
这是唯一的解释
It's the only explanation.
那只是你扭曲的头脑,能想到的唯一解释
No,it's the only,explanation your twisted mind
你对无法找到答案而暴跳如雷
can come up with because,you're angry that you can't find the answer,
想拿她出气
and you're taking it out on her.
你却只是因为幼稚和浪漫维护一个陌生人
And you are protecting a complete stranger,based on some childishly romantic notion
比如婚姻总是幸福的,人们不会自相残杀
that people are all so happily married,they don't want to kill each other.
你说我幼稚?
You calling me childish?
-该长大了,-都给我闭嘴
- Grow up.- Shut up. Both of you.
离他老婆远点
And stay away from his wife.
对不起,我不能同意你去侵犯别人
Sorry. I'm not giving you,permission to assault someone.
怎么了?
Let's see.
我看到...
I'm thinking...
芥末上校(美国电影clue的主角),在一个放着蜡烛架的音乐室里
colonel mustard in the music room,with the candlestick.
并不是什么音乐室
There's no music room.
那是一个音乐学校
It's the conservatory.
- 不一样么,-不一样
- Same thing.- No,it isn'T.
如果我们找不出她到底用了什么
If we don't find out,what she's using
立即开始治疗,他会在一周内死亡
and start treatment immediately,,he'll be dead in a week.
如果你是对的话
If you're right.
如果头是对的,你等于强奸了一个无辜的妇女
If foreman's right,you'd have,basically raped an innocent woman.
我妻子解雇了女佣
My wife fired the maid.
显然她想要使所有让她想起我的东西消失
Apparently she's getting rid of,everything that reminds her of me.
你上了女佣?
You did your maid?
只是对她很好
I was nice to our maid,
这使我妻子非常恼火,天晓得为什么
which... annoyed her.God knows why.
-可能你妻子上了她,-没有人上她
Maybe she was doing her.No one was doing her.
明白了?
All right?
但是你想要对此负责
But,you still feel responsible.
即使没有人被上,这仍然是你的错
Even though nothing or no one was done,,it's still your fault.
我想要继续付她工钱,直到她找到工作
I offered to keep paying her salary,until she found another job.
但是她不干活就坚决不收一分钱,所以...
But she refused to take any money,without doing any work,so-
想要雇人打扫房间么?
want someone to clean your apartment?
我付钱.
It's on me.
你应该搬出去而不是搬更多的人进来
You're supposed to moving out,,not moving more people in.
她不是搬进来,她只是打扫卫生
She's not moving in.She's gonna clean.
也许我应该搬出去然后你们就可以...
Maybe I should just move out,,and the the two of you-
我的上帝
oh,god!
- 我的上帝,不,- 紧急情况!
- Oh,god,no.- call a code!
360伏电压,给他做EPI
Charge it to 360.Give him epi.
充电完毕!
Clear!
-还是没有脉搏,- 充电
- Still no pulse.- Charging.
充电完毕!
Clear!
有脉搏了
I got a pulse.
瞳孔有反应
Pupils are reactive.
能听见么?
You still with us?
他缺氧不到一分钟
He was without oxygen,for less than a minute.
不是氧气不足
It can't be hypoxia.
可能是中风
Could be a stroke.
亲爱的,能听见么?
Honey,can you hear me?
Bob,跟我说话. Bob?
Bob,talk to me. Bob?
亲爱的,求求你
Honey,please.
Bob,能听见么?
Bob,can you hear me?
- 他醒了,- 能听见么?
- He's awake.- Can you hear me?
亲爱的?
Honey?
她可真是个好演员
Yes. She is...quite the little actress.
那么我们假设她没有下毒
So let's say,she's not poisoning him.
没什么好讨论的了
There's nothing more to discuss.
先是肺和肾衰竭,然后是神经性症状,现在又是心脏停止跳动
We've got lung and kidney failure,,neurological symptoms, and now cardiac arrest.
狼疮的定义就是影响到多器官,的系统性疾病
A systemic disease with multi-organ,involvement is the definition of lupus.
自动免疫性抑制没起作用
autoimmune suppressants aren't helping.
应该试试环磷酰胺(一种抗肿瘤药),看看有没有效果
We should start him on cyclophosphamide.See if it makes a difference.
没错
Yeah.
还有干扰素
And interferon.
干扰素可不是治疗狼疮的方法
Interferon isn't,an approved treatment for lupus.
你不会还以为..
You're not still thinking-
干扰素也不是治疗重金属中毒的方法
interferon isn't an approved,treatment for heavy metal toxicity either.
但是这是治疗病毒感染的唯一方法
But it's pretty much the only,thing we can do for a viral infection.
- 我们没有想到是因为,- 这不可能,他没有发烧
- We didn't consider it because-,- because it doesn't make sense. There's no fever.
因为免疫系统已经失灵了
Because he's got no immune system.
这多亏了你治疗狼疮用的免疫抑制剂
Thanks to the immunosuppressants,you prescribed for lupus treatment.
他刚住院时也没有发烧
He didn't present,with a fever either.
因为那是在病毒引起的自免疫反应之后
Because at that point,,he was a post-viral autoimmune reaction.
同样地
Which again-
多亏了治疗狼疮用的免疫抑制剂
thanks to the immunosuppressants,you prescribed for lupus treatment,
他的免疫系统基本上成为了滋生病毒的温床
his immune system basically rolled,out the red carpet for the dormant virus,
把病毒激活,引起感染,给他用干扰素
waking it up,turning it into a present,viral infection. Give him interferon.
但是如果这是狼疮,干扰素会使他更加糟糕
But if it is lupus,,interferon could make it worse.
会进一步抑制骨髓功能
Suppress his bone marrow even further.
哪个更有可能?,使用类固醇治疗
Which is more likely?,A rapidly progressing,
但发作极快的自发性狼疮可能性大
acute-onset lupus in a patient,who's already on steroids,
还是一个医生团队遗漏了,病毒感染的可能性大
or a team of doctors,missing a post-viral reaction?
我们并没有遗漏什么
We didn't miss anything.
好吧,那我是错的,给他用干扰素!
Well then,I'm wrong and you shouldn't-,give him interferon!
静脉内注射干扰素对一些,病毒感染很有效果
intravenous interferon has been shown,to be effective against some viral infections.
但是你说过这不是感染
But,I thought you said,it wasn't an infection.
你说这是狼疮
You said it was lupus.
越来越严重的症状让我们重新诊断
The increasingly rapid progression of,the symptoms has caused us to reconsider.
如果你们还是错的呢?
And what if you're wrong here too?
如果并不是病毒的原因
What if it's not a virus?
用干扰素的确存在风险
There are risks with interferon.
特别是对一个早就没有,免疫功能的病人来说
Especially in a patient,who's already immunosuppressed.
你看,现在这个时候,肺部,肾脏,还有心脏都在不断衰竭
Look,at this point,you're lungs,kidneys,,and heart are all failing.
我们已经没有其他选择了
We really don't have any choice.
我作弊了
I cheated.
什么?
What?
9年级的时候,地理课上
9th grade... earth science.
Foley先生
Mr. Foley.
我坐在你身后,这样就可以偷看你
I sat behind you,so I could cheat off of you.
我让你偷看的...
And I let you cheat...
这样你就会坐在我身后
so you'd sit behind me.
我以为我们会白头偕老
I thought we were,gonna grow old together.
- 9年级,- 不,是10年级
- In 9th grade?,- No. 10th.
怎么,你想让我先追你?
What,you had to,make sure I put out first?
不
No.
我知道你在7年级就想追我
I knew you put out in the 7th grade.
我爱你
I love you.
我知道
Yeah,I know.
说你爱我
Say you love me.
我不说
No.
为什么不说
Why not?
因为你不会死的
Because... you're not dying.
说你爱我
Say it anyway.
你不想让我伤害你吧?
You gonna make me hurt you?
我爱你
I love you.
这不起作用
it's not working.
他的肺和肾还在不断恶化
Both his lungs and kidneys,are continuing to deteriorate.
加大剂量,早加大了
Up the dose.We already have.
显然还不够
Apparently not enough.
我不认为是病毒
I don't think it's a virus. 
我们已经进行了所有的测定,全都是阴性
We've been titers for everything,we could think of. They're all negative.
加大干扰素的剂量
Increase the interferon.
House,有更好的主意么?
House. You got a better idea?
- 除了狼疮?,- 没有
- Other than lupus?,- No.
那么加大剂量
Then up the dose.
和 Lambert先生和太太约定的时间是在一小时以前
Mr. And mrs. Lambert's appointment,was over an hour ago.
对不起.我病了而且我的团队需要我去紧急会诊
Sorry. I was sick.
你太太患有疱疹
Your wife has herpes.
什么?
What?
那,那不可能,我没有任何...
That- that's impossible.I don't have any-
你没有任何外遇...目前来说
you haven't had an outbreak... yet.
放心,你会有的
Don't worry,you will.
你这个混蛋
You rutty jackass!
我?20年来我没和任何人上过床
Me? I haven't been,with anyone in 20 years!
但你的那个上有疱疹
But you're the one,with the blisters on his-
不代表他先得病
doesn't mean,that he got it first.
并不一定要通过外遇才能传染
You don't need to have an,outbreak to spread the virus.
对阿!,你才是那个整天吵着要更多的性生活的人
Yeah!And you're the one,always talking about wanting more sex.
那是和你
From you.
如果你没有在外面胡来,可能能让我满足
And maybe I'd get more if you,weren't actually getting it somewhere else.
好吧,看来你们显然有好多话想说
Well,you two obviously,have a lot to talk about.
别想把这个烂摊子推给我
Don't even think about,dumping this on my lap.
肯定有方法可以证明是他
There's gotta be someway,to prove that it's him.
我很抱歉,没有这样的测试
I'm sorry. There is no test.
你们有没有曾经使用过公用坐便器?
Either you two ever sit on a public toilet?
- 有么?,- 当然有了
- Well?,- Of course.
疱疹病毒在短时间内可以在体外存活
Herpes can live for short,periods of time outside the body.
House医生,你知道你不会通过
Dr. House,you know,you can't get herpes-
一些小心谨慎的医生会告诉你
some politically,correct doctors will tell you
从坐便器上感染病毒是不可能的
that it's impossible to,get infected by a toilet seat,
但他们也会告诫你不要在外遇时,使用一块毛巾擦你的胯部和脸
but they'll also tell you not to use,the same bath towel to dry your crotch
- 发现矛盾了没?,- 我一直使用一次性纸盖
and your face during an outbreak.
- 一直?,- 是的,那当然
- Always?,- Yes,of course.
- 你呢?,- 我不会
- What about you?,- No.
我从来都不知道
I never knew.
哦,我的天,这太匪夷所思了
Oh,please.This is ridiculous.
他妈的,我确定这是个骗局
Damn.I was sure it was miyagi.
什么?
What?
他是相信会从坐便器传染
He could believe that,you can herpes from a toilet seat,
还是他有外遇而正好有一个很好的借口
or he could be cheating on you,and just be happy to have an out.
坐便器是一种可能性,不是么?
The toilet seat makes sense,doesn't it?
当然是,但是如果她是清白的,她一定不会相信这么完美的谎言
Sure,but she'd,only refused to believe
既然你们两个都不是清白的
And since you both,can't be innocent...
你这个混蛋
you rutty jackass.
你...
Oh,you-
- 太感谢了,-不客气
- Thanks a lot.- My pleasure.
亲爱的,等等我
Honey. Wait!
还不错
Not bad.
她是不是患有遗传性关节炎?
She has a family,history of arthritis,doesn't she?
是的,没错,怎么了?
Yeah,she does. What does-?
停止使用干扰素
Stop the interferon.
在做一次重金属排查,这次试试黄金
Do another heavy metal screen.Only this time,test for gold.
你不会还是认为她...
You don't still think that she-
不要让她进卫生间
and don't let her go to the bathroom.
为什么你会在意她...
Why would you care if she-
喂?
Hello?
我叫Lady.
I'm lady.
你都干了些什么?
What did you do to my closet?
只是打扫了一下
I cleaned it.
Wilson医生说可以打扫
Uh,dr. Wilson said,that I could go ahead-
这不是 Wilson医生的衣橱
it's not dr. Wilson's closet!
木头盒子在哪?
Where's the wood box?
- 木头盒子?,-对,木头盒子
- A wood box?,- Yes,the wood box.
木头做的像个盒子
I's made of wood,,and it's box-shaped.
从我搬进来的那天就一直,放在衣橱的最里面
It's been in the back of,this closet since the day I moved in.
- 没见过任何的木头...- 你可能没注意
- I didn't see any kind of wood-,- you may not have seen it,
但是你已经动过了,问题是在哪?
but you've obviously med it.The question is where?
我没动过任何东西,我只是...
Well,I did not move anything,,I just-
听着,它一直在衣橱里,你来了它却不在了
look,it was in this closet.Then you came now it's not in this closet.
- 什么样的盒子?,- 木头的!木头的!
- What type of box?,- Wood!Wood!
棕色的木头箱子,顶上有个金属把手
It's a brown wood box.It's got a metal handle on the top.
看起来就像...就像是一个工具箱
It looks like a-,like a tackle or a toolbox.
哦,你是说箱子吧?
Ah,you mean the chest?
在床底下的那个?
The one that's under the bed?
想要修理什么东西?
Do you need to fix something?
恩,多谢你
Um. Thanks.
那好吧,我去其他楼层
Well,fine,,then I'll go to one on another floor.
实际上,都无法使用了
Well,actually,,they're not working there either.
医院的所有厕所全都坏了?
Every bathroom in the,whole hospital is out of order?
恩,他们...
Well,they're,um-
-那个水...- 我要去卫生间
- the water-,- I'm going to the bathroom.
- 她在哪?,-她一定要去卫生间
- Where is she?,- She had to go to the bathroom.
-我说了不要让她去的,- 我能怎么办?把她绑起来?
- I told you not to let her.- What was I supposed to do? Tie her up?
为什么不?她喜欢这一套
Why not?She likes that.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
你的手是湿的
Uh,your hand is wet.
对不起,太紧张了
Sorry. Must be nervous.
有几个坏消息
I got some bad news.
什么坏消息?
What?
你丈夫肺部的损伤是永久性的
The damage to your,husband's lungs is permanent.
肾脏损伤可以恢复,如果治疗得当
The kidney damage is reversible,,and with the right therapy,
所有的神经系统功能也能恢复
he should regain full neurological function.
如果不参加什么马拉松比赛就不会有事
Us other than the fact that he's not gonna,be running any marathons,he should be fine.
但是这是好消息,不是么?
But that's good news,isn't it?
我还没说完
I'm not finished.
小时候
When I was a kid,
我父亲在埃及的一个陆军基地里服役
my dad was stationed,in a marine base in egypt.
周围一片荒芜
We were in the middle of no where,
小孩没什么事情可做除了..
and there was absolutely nothing,for a kid to do except...
- 寻找木乃伊的坟墓,- 你不想让我上卫生间
- look for a mummy's tomb.- You didn't want me to go to the bathroom
只是因为你想说我的丈夫会康复
because you wanted to tell me,my husband is going to be fine
而你曾经住在埃及?
and that... you used to live in egypt?
不是不让你上厕所
I didn't have a problem,with you going to the bathroom.
只是不想让你洗手
I just didn't want,you to wash your hands.
事实上我从没找到过木乃伊
I never actually found a mummy.
但学到了许多古代埃及人的知识
But,I did learn a fair amount,about the ancient egyptians.
比如,他们发现氯化锡
For example,they discovered,that stannous chloride
不仅可以增加红玻璃的强度
is not only great for toughening ruby glass,
而且在混合了黄金之后会变成亮紫色
but if it's mixed with gold,,it turns bright purple.
要么你的手指是用黄金做的
Now either,your fingers,actually are worth their weight in gold,
要么你一直丈夫的麦片里,撒上硫化钠和黄金
or you've been sprinkling your husband's,cereal with gold sodium thiomalate.
这是一种关节炎疗法,不过美国已经绝迹了
It's an arthritis remedy that,it's rarely used here in the in the U.S.
但是在墨西哥还是很流行的
But it's still popular in mexico.
应该表扬一下
Gotta give you props.
我从没见人用黄金下毒
I've never heard of,anyone using gold before.
这简直...富有诗意
It's almost... poetic.
太荒谬了
It's ridiculous.
黄金毒素试验说明了一切
Heavy metal tox screen,for gold was off the chart.
-为什么我要...-因为你想要杀了他
- Why would I-,- because you were trying to kill him.
很想知道隐藏为什么之后的为什么
I'd love to know,the why behind that why.
但你不会说的,不是么?
But,you're not gonna tell me,are you?
你错了.我...
You're wrong. I-
我爱bob.
I love bob.
我没说你不爱他
I never said you didn't love him.
怎么会这样?
How does somebody do that?
不分昼夜坐在床边,帮助他
Sit by someone's bedside,day and night,helping them,
安慰他,同时想要杀了他
comforting them,,and at the same time killing them.
可能他有外遇了
Maybe he was having an affair.
可能她有外遇了
Maybe she was having an affair.
也可能她只是从看着他受苦中取乐,看着他的生命一点一点慢慢流逝
Or maybe she just gets her kicks,out of slowly sucking the life out of a guy,
他一定做了什么坏事
watching him suffer.
- 是的,他造成了一切,-我没说这是他活该
- Yeah,he had it coming.- I didn't say he deserved it.
他唯一的一件错事就是,和不爱社交的人结婚
The only thing he did wrong,was marry a sociopath.
或者她只是厌倦了婚姻生活
Or maybe she just,got tired of being married.
不想对家庭和朋友承认
Didn't want to admit to family and friends
人人都觉得幸福的婚姻事实上并不幸福
that the marriage everyone,thought was perfect wasn't.
不需要有人看着她?,她要逃跑怎么办?
Shouldn't of us stay with her?,What is she tries to run?
对. Cameron,你回去看着她.
Yeah. Cameron,go back there.
我们都在女人的房间会显得很奇怪
It'd be weird,if we were all in the ladies' room.
二巯基丙醇(一种解毒剂)复合疗法
we started chelation,therapy with dimercaprol.
听起来很不错
Thrilled to hear it.
他的肾功能没有好转
His kidney function,hasn't improved.
会好的
It will.
他的肺需要移植
He's gonna need,a lung transplant.
他会更迷人,不是么?
He's becoming more attractive,by the minute,isn't he?
你很满意这个结果
You're pleased.
你证明了所有的婚姻都是一个错误
You think you've proved,every marriage is a mistake.
我看起来很满意?
Do I look pleased?
否认是一种幸福
Ignorance is bliss.
Love and happiness
wait a minute,something goin' wrong
someone's on the phone
3:00 in the mornin'
yeah
talkin' about how,she can make it right,yeah
well
"James Wilson财产, 擅动将遭起诉",happiness is when you,really feel good about somebody
happiness is when you,really feel good about somebody
there's nothin' wrong
bein' in love with someone
yeah,yeah
oh,baby
你有一个新的留言
you have one new message.
你好,我是Blake Hanson,我找Wilson医生
hi,this is blake hanson,calling for dr. Wilson.
有人出了更高的租金
I got a better offer,for the apartment.
我说过要租给你
Now,I know offered it to you already,
所以如果你也出这个价就租给你了
so if you match the offer,,you can still have the place.
千万别忘了明天一早就打电话给我
Make sure you call me first,thing in the morning and let me know,
否则...你知道我的号码的
otherwise,well, you got my number.
Make you do right
and love will make you do wrong
love and happiness
留言已删除
message deleted.